

Shukhratjon Yuldashev

Financial Developer

Profile

I have been working on integration and automation of financial programs for 3 years.

To date, I have worked on more than 10 successful projects. Among them are "Elma", "Formula Motor Oil Company", "Baraka" market, "Alkan" furniture market, and "Sadaf" dairy products.

In 2020, I started working for ELMAKON and in 2021, I was hired by SOFTWARE SYSTEMS as a JAVA and 1C programmer. Currently I am working with these 2 companies.

Those project is still being updated and optimized, and they are still used by various reputable companies.

Education

Tashkent University of Information Technology 2019 - current

Mass-media

Work Experience

Software Systems | March 2021 - Current

Java, 1C developer

• automation of business processes

Elmakon | June 2020 - current

1C, PHP developer

• integration and automation of the whole system

Skills

- · Problem solving
- Knowledge of algorithms and data structures
- Proficiency in troubleshooting software issues and debugging a large codebase
- Software programming languages

Technology

- Java OOP, CORE, SPRING, SPRING BOOT, WEB HOOK, SOCKET:
- PHP8 SYMFONY, LARAVEL;
- Python, MACHINE LEARNING 101, NUMPY, DATA ENGINEERING;
- Platforms above 1C 8.3, any mode, REST API, ODATA, XDTO;
- Database -> SQL / NOSQL mastered

ADDRESS

Chilonzor 10, Tashkent

EMAIL

webdeveloper0106@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://alifcoder.uz

SOCIAL MEDIA

@alif_coder